<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="0.91">
  <channel>
    <title>Quintonn's Blog</title>
    <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>My personal blog</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <title>Quintonn's blog</title>
      <url>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/images/white-icon-code.png</url>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/</link>
      <width>24</width>
      <height>24</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Super Rugby 2020 Kicks Off</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/rugby/super_rugby_2020_week_1</link>
      <description>The start of the 2020 Super Rugby Season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Added Comments And RSS Features To My Blog</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/blog/adding_disqus_and_rss_feeds</link>
      <description>In this post I explain how I added comments to my blog and also the ability for readers to subscribe using either RSS feeds or with email</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Dynamic Private NuGet Feed with Authentication</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/programming/my_own_private_nuget_feed</link>
      <description>In this post I explain how I setup a private nuget to host multiple repositories with the ability to authenticate reads and writes to each repository.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Using Gmail for Work!</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/general/stop_using_gmail_for_work</link>
      <description>In this post I discuss why you should stop using free email accounts like Gmail for work or professional purposes and instead setup an email account using your own custom domain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up My Raspberry Pi as a VPN Gateway</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/raspberry_pi/raspberry_pi_vpn_gateway</link>
      <description>In this post I show how I setup my Raspberry Pi as a VPN gateway for my XBOX to connect through so I can buy and play games in the country where I purchased my XBOX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporting Markdown In InstaBlog</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/blog/supporting_markdown</link>
      <description>I've added the ability to write blog entries using Markdown, and it has made a huge difference. It's much easier than writing HTML code. In this post I talk about how I managed to achieve that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating a Hg repo to Git</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/programming/migrate_a_hg_repo_to_git</link>
      <description>In this post I go through the steps and process to easily migrate a Hg repository to Git, including the entire commit history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Sourcing My Web Server Framework</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/programming/open_sourcing_my_web_framework</link>
      <description>I decided to open source a project I've been working on for the last 5 or 6 years. It's a .NET platform for building web servers, CMS, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Similarities Between Tragedy And Luck</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/philosophy/tragedy_and_luck</link>
      <description>A car accident in the town made me realize people react to other people's fortune and tragedy in a very similar way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm Looking For A Business Partner</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/programming/looking_for_a_business_partner</link>
      <description>I am working on a mobile application and platform and I'm looking for someone to join me on this adventure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Buy Naked Options</title>
      <link>https://quintonn.github.io/blog/#!/entry/trading/do_not_buy_naked_options</link>
      <description>I believe buying naked options, in trading, is almost never a good idea. And in this post I explain my opinion with a brief Netflix example.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
